OMODIBO LOIS ESIMEHRO

Mobile Line: +234-706 552 2701 +234-811 5596 487

· Email: loisomodibo@gmail.com

Career Objective

My objective is to work in a professional environment where my skills are valued and can benefit the organization and where I can continually improve my skills and build on my expertise to add value to the organization and to society at large.

Professional Summary

I have a strong passion for Web development and a solid foundation in HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, and React. With a keen eye for design and a commitment to creating intuitive user experiences, I strive to contribute to the development of visually appealing and user–friendly websites and applications.

Experience

STUTERN GRADUATE ACCELERATOR

Nov 2022 to Present

Frontend Developer Responsibilities:

- Building user-facing portion of websites and web applications using Html, CSS and JavaScript.
- Implementing responsive design to ensure compatibility with various devices and browsers
- Translating design concepts and wireframes into functional and interactive user interfaces.
- Creating Visually appealing layouts, components and animations to enhance user experience.
- Worked with frameworks such as React.

PRESTIGE CODING MENTORSHIP

Sep 2022 to Nov 2022

Frontend Mentor Responsibilities:

• Teach young developers Html, CSS and JavaScript.

RED PLUS PHARMACY LIMITED.

Jan. 2022 to Aug 2022

Administrative Manager Responsibilities:

- - I follow up with all company's documentation.
 - I prepare drugs and execute prescription orders for collection or delivery.
 - I maintain an approved drug and controlled substance list and verify expiry date.
 - I oversee the daily business operations of the pharmacy, sales assistants, cashiers, shelf stockers and other pharmacy employees.
 - I manage the inventory.
 - I address customers' complaints and request.
 - I verify prescription details with the healthcare specialist who prescribed them, when required.
 - I monitor products displayed on shelves, and as well as the general appearance of the pharmacy.
 - I establish and implement internal controls, and administrative systems, policies and procedures to ensure that the firm's day to day operational activities are effective.
 - I developed employees contract, code of conduct for staffs
 - I worked closely with medical personnel in seeing that prescriptions are filled correctly and services provided as needed.
 - I ensure the safe storage of prescription drugs and controlled substances.

SWIVEL CODES LTD.

Sep. 2021 to Jan. 2022

Finance and Administrative Manager Responsibilities:

- I was responsible for overall financial management, budgeting and monitoring of project expenditures.
- I followed up with all company's documentation,
- I schedule and plan meetings.
- I establish and implement internal controls, and administrative systems, policies and procedures to ensure that the firm's day to day operational activities are effective.
- I developed employees contract, code of conduct for staffs
- I ensured

SCILLAFIELD SOLUTIONS LTD.

July 2021 - Sep. 2021

Assistant Projects Officer

Responsibilities:

- I assist associates to analyze, plan and develop requirements and standards in reference to scheduled projects.
- I monitor daily tasks, and ensure all associates are actively working towards established milestones.
- I set up regular technical team meetings to determine progress and address any questions or challenges regarding projects

- I define clear deliverables, roles and responsibilities for staff members required for specific projects or initiatives.
- I write proposal documents for specific projects

SCILLAFIELD SOLUTIONS LTD.

Mar. 2021 - July 2021

Finance and Administrative Manager

I helped the firm manage financial and administration activities to achieve financial goals.

Responsibilities:

- I ensure the preparation and maintenance of all financial records.
- I supervise and manage payroll processing and tax filling activities.
- I monitor and manage expenditures with allotted budget
- I identify and resolve financial and administrative issues
- I schedule and plan meetings and appointments
- I establish and implement internal controls, and administrative systems, policies and procedures to ensure that the firm's day to day operational activities are effective.
- Prepares and presents quarterly and yearly financial budgets and cash flow forecasts, and works with Co-Directors to actively monitor and understand budget variances.

SCILLAFIELD SOLUTIONS LTD.

Nov. 2020 - Mar. 2021

Office Assistant

I help the firm acquire and implement projects by supporting associates to initiate and maintain customer relationship and track the execution of project activities.

Responsibilities:

- I assist associates to optimize their outputs by developing and sharing weekly reports.
- I coordinate weekly meetings to plan the activities for every week and follow up with deliverables
- I assist the administration department to communicate internal information to the relevant department.
- I schedule and plan meetings and appointments
- I manage internal procurement, monitor stock levels to ensure that office supplies are always available.
- I coordinate with other departments to ensure compliance with established policies
- I conduct verification exercises for vendors by reviewing their registration documents

NIGERIAN METEOROLOGICAL AGENCY (NIMET), Kano

Nov. 2017 to Oct. 2018

Administrative Officer (NYSC)

I assisted associates to optimize output by coordinating resources and ensuring timely and specific execution of operation.

Responsibilities:

- I communicated corporate objectives across all divisions through regular correspondence and scheduled follow up.
- I monitored and evaluated personnel performance to complete reviews, recommend advancement or address productivity concerns.
- I established efficient workflow processes.
- I assisted senior administrative professionals with daily work tasks.
- I coordinated domestic and international travel arrangement.

NATIONAL ENVIRONMENT STANDARD REGULATORY AND ENFORCEMENT AGENCY (NESREA), CDS Group, Kano.

Nov. 2017 to Oct. 2018

Member, Sanitation Sensitization Team

Responsibilities:

- I carried out periodic community assessments on sanitation and hygiene practices to identify areas for interventions.
- Promote community led sanitation and hygiene programs through awareness creation, establishment and maintenance of functional community based supporting structures.
- Support establishment and implementation of health and hygiene promotion activities in schools.
- Conduct training as well as extend guidance and technical support to the community based hygiene and sanitation promotion structures.
- Compile weekly, monthly and periodic plans and report on general sanitation and hygiene projects.
- Perform any other duties as assigned by the supervisors.
- I conduct verification exercises for vendors by reviewing their registration documents

Skills

- Proficient Oral and Written Communicator
- Client Relations
- Document Control
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel & Power-point).

Attention to detail

Professional/ Societal affiliations

- Certified Member, Teachers Registration Council of Nigeria, July 2016
- Training on Microsoft Office Suite, Microbytes College, Lagos, 2011
- Stutern Graduate Accelerator, 2022

Research/Theses

 The Effect and Advantages of Chemistry Laboratory in Secondary School A case study of Abraka Grammar School, Abraka, Delta State, December 2016

Education

DELTA STATE UNIVERSITY, ABRAKA, DELTA STATE, NIGERIA (2012 - 2017)

BSC, CHEMISTRY EDUCATION (Second Class Lower)

FIRST ZION HIGH SCHOOL, LAGOS NIGERIA (2006 - 2012)

• WEST AFRICAN SENIOR SCHOOL CERTIFICATE, 2012

Hobbies

- Sewing
- Cooking
- Reading

Referees

Abdullahi Raheem

Program Associate

Scillafield solutions ltd <u>Abdullahi.Raheem@scillafield.com.ng</u>

Tel: +243 810 6219 879